A Guide to the Records of George Bernard Lorraine, ca. 1925-1976
Library of Virginia
- Real estate records (Box 1-149)
  - Virginia real estate (Box 1-146)
    - Buckingham County (Box 12, Folder 10-29)
      - Peary Hill: Alexander S. Hall, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Pleasant Shade: Virginia Forbes Hutchings, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - Saratoga: Everett Hammond, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - Tavern: B.R. West, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - Bradshaw, W.C.: 540 acres, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - Culbreth, H.W.: 1952 (Box 12, Folder 24)
      - Eldridge, G.W.: 1943 (Box 12, Folder 25)
      - James, E.C.: 1942-1943 (Box 12, Folder 26)
      - Wood, Mr.: 100 acres, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 27)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1932-1967 (Box 12, Folder 28)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Campbell County (Box 13, Folder 1-5)
      - Lake Haven Lodge and Cove Point Lodge: L.B. Montague, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Oakdale: H.L. Jennings, 1947-1953 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - White Hall: Chillie Langhorne, 1949-1954 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Burch, Thomas G. (realtor): 7000 acres, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Caroline County (Box 13-16)
      - Aspen Hill: J. Davis Henderson, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Blenheim: Retta G.H. Lowry, 1935-1946 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Caroline Inn: John H. Ahlers, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Chestnut Valley: R.E. Bell, 1936-1960 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Elmwood: Josephine J. McCuen, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Elson Green: Garland W. Flourney, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Hampton Manor: J.W. Brehm, 1934-1943 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Hayfield: Amy G. Bassett, 1931-1940 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Haymont: H.H. Gatewood, 1934-1946 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Hazelwood: Hazel C. Garrett, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Hickory Grove: S.S. Ambrose, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Holly Springs: J.W. Whaley, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - La Grange: G.E. Garnett, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Magnolia or Magnolia Farm: J.R. Hairston, 1936-1943 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Meadows: P.S. Hart, 1933-1937 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Mount Gideon: A. Gerald Bush, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Mount View: Dr. James P. Broaddus, 1937-1938 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - North Wales: J. Louis Reynolds, 1941-1953 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Oak Grove: George Butter Pollard, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Oak Ridge: Bank and Union Trust Company, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Old Pollard Tract: 1968 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Pine Needle Tavern: Henrietta Selby, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Pleasant Retreat: 100 acres, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Popular Grove: Colonel T.H. Chambers, 1936-1946 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Prospect Hill: Clifford S. Gage, 1946-1947 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - Rock Stop Farm: Helen Hull Jacobs, 1937-1948, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - Santee: Eugene F. Castles, 1941-1954 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Shannon Mills: New York Life Insurance Company, 1932-1951 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Singing River Plantation: Mrs. Curtis Drake Cecil, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - South Brook: M.E. Coverdale, 1951-1953 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Sparta: 3 1/2 acres, 1969-1971 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Spring Grove: J.W. DeJarnette, 1940-1941 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Spring Hill: W.A. Vaughan, 1938-1939 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Spring Hill: W.H. Brown, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Sycamore Hill: Hugh Rose, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Thornberry Farm: H.H. George, Jr., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Tompson's Hill: L.A. Lawrence, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Townfields Farm: C.A. Brown, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Townfield: Bernard I. Driscoll, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Virginia Tearoom: R.D. Parks, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Woodpecker: 365 acres, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Yew Springs: S. Kirker, 1930's (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Allen, E.C.: 24 acres, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Ayers, J.E. and Mamie: 50 acres, 1934-1938 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Campbell, J.P.: 2 acres, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Carlton, R.T.: 465 acres, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Collins, J.B.: 193 acres, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Elliott, Z.C.: 150 acres, 1942-1943 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Farrish, F.B.: 1946-1947 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Fennell, William: 25 acres, 1953-1956 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Head, Dr. L.J.: 324 acres, 1935 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Ruppert, Mrs.: 10 1/2 acres, 1945 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Smith, Clara: 1936, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Taliaferro, W.G.: 104 acres, 1936 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Winder, Arthur L.: 202 acres, 1935 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Winder, Arthur L.: 36 acres, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1932-1942, 1954-1963 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings - Bowling Green, Virginia (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings - Port Royal, Virginia (Box 16, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Charles City County (Box 17-18)
      - Berkeley Mills and Tea Room: Archer Jones, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Bush Hill: Mrs. Walls, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Edgewood: Leo F. Marks, 1944, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Farmers Rest: R.W. Duke, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Glebe: Grant Dening, 1935-1968 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Greenway and Gunno: F.H. Avery, 1932 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Green Yard Farm: Greif Brothers Cooperage Corporation, 1936-1940 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Indian Fields and Big Buckland: J.A. Ruffin, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Laurel Hill Dairy Farm: Joe Aignon, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Meadow Springs: C.G. Avery, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Mount Sterling: n.d. (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - River Edge: Sam A. Mason, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Sherwood Forest: Gardener Tyler, 1932 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Westbury: T.H. Dougherty, 1941-1942 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Westover: Bruce C. Fisher, 1957-1958 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Weyanoke or Lower Weyanoke: 700 acres, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Wilcox Neck: B. Adamson, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Wilcox Wharf: Wilette K. Lamar, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Wilcox Wharf or All View: T.N. Hubbard, 1941 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Deitrich, E.A.: 3 1/2 acres, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Gamble, R.A.: 20 acres, 1959-1961 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Martin, L.G.: 3 acres, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Wobie, Mr.: 18 acres, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1940-1959 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Charlotte County (Box 18-19)
      - Charlotte: S.D. Laughlin, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Do-Well Plantation: Elizabeth B. Gavies, 1937-1956 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Gravel Hill: Rufus C. Phillips, Jr., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Ingleside: J.W. Daniels, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Moldavia: Ruth Lee Fish, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Moldavia: Thomas R. Watkins (realtor), 1965-1967 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Oakland: Mrs. Ormonde Smith, 1950-1952 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Old State Farm: Old Belt Realty Company, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Old Venable Place: Baylor B. Shackleford, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Holt, W.B.: 600 acres, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Watkins, Mrs.: 45 acres, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1975 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Charlottesville (Box 19, Folder 11-12)
      - Early, F.R.: 1947 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Stevens, William T.: 185 acres, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Chesterfield County (Box 19-22)
      - Arnolda: 242 acres, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Belmont Lake: 1940 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - British Camp Farm: 1953 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Brooks: 1955 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Castlewood: J.H. Lumpkin, Jr., 1947 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Cedar Grove: Tom Elliott, 1946-1947 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Eppington: William Hinds, 1931-1958 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Fairafar Farm: Frank W. Corley, 1931-1934 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Farm Hill or Burfoot Farm: T.D. Burfott, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Fox Dean Farm: L.C. Burt, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Glenconner: L.W. Beroset, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Greenfield: J.E. Trevillian, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Guernsdale: Charles Stein, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Homeland: J.A. Bass, 1953-1960 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Magnolia Grange: Philip Cogbill, 1951 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Matoaka Manor: J.W. Jacob, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Montevideo: 1939 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Moody Tavern: A.C. Childress, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Mount Eagle: A.J.T. Wendt, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Murchie Mill: Mrs. John K. Messersmith, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Oak Hill: H.C. Canada, Jr., 1949-1950 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Old Cole Home or Robinson Place: E. Lawrence Keirn, 1949-1950 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Old Howlet Farm: A.W. Hodder, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Olive Hill: R.L. Crumpler, 1936, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Olive Hill: F.G. Wall, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Physic Hill: Frank Robius, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - Pine Knot: William P. Carhart, 1948-1954 (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - Robert E. Lee Motor Court: R.E.R. Goyne, 1949-1953 (Box 20, Folder 21)
      - Roslyn Farm: Des Portes, 1942 (Box 20, Folder 22)
      - Short Dairy Farm: 1954 (Box 20, Folder 23)
      - Trabue Tavern: Ruby Inge, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Wilkinson's Tavern: 1955 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Wood Place: 1939 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Woodland: Edward L. Colston, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Bellwood, E.C.: 800 acres, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Corpening, Adah: 691 acres, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Cox, Mr.: 27 acres, 1930's (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Duke, M.M.: 50 acres, 1934-1935 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - French, Mrs.: 25 acres, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Galvin, Mrs.: 205 acres, 1934-1936 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Gray, C.H.: 10 acres, 1936 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Hawkins, J.E.: 292 acres, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Hill, H.L.: 5 acres, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Hines, V.L.: 5 acres, 1941-1942 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Knickerbocker, E.E.: 68 acres, 1934 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Leonard, Floyd: 21 acres, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Miller, Mr.: 1949 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Peck, Mr.: 3 acres, 1930's (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Pointer, W.J.: 69 acres, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Polley, E.F.: 50 acres, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Rudd, Charles E.: 1934-1935 (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Sampson, W.H.: 1962 (Box 21, Folder 22)
      - Smith, P.C.: 53 acres, 1928-1938 (Box 21, Folder 23)
      - Winfree, J.W.: 89 acres, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 24)
      - Wray, Mrs. John M.: 1951 (Box 21, Folder 25)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1933-1938, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 26)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1931-1939 (Box 21, Folder 27)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
    - Clarke County (Box 22, Folder 3-5)
      - Dearmont Hall: Stuart E. Brown, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Wolf-Marsh: Mrs. Thomson Sowers, 1945 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Colonial Heights (Box 22, Folder 6-8)
      - Appomatico: William H. Lewis, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Oak Hill: 1948 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Oak Hill: Mrs. Raymond Perkinson, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Craig County (Box 22, Folder 9-12)
      - Craigland Farm: 2000 acres, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Burrows, C.G.: 700 acres, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Fielder, C.L.: 309 acres, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Culpeper County (Box 22-23)
      - Hazelmere: M.G. Marsh, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - La Grange: Preston Browning (realtor), 1962 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Milton: P.M. Humphrey, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - Mountain View: Fanny Norris, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 16)
      - Muckamoor: William R. Thompson, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 17)
      - Quiet Shade: John M. Garnet, 1938-1943 (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Quiet Shade: Joseph M. Samuels (realtor), 1950 (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - Sherwood: E.O. Willis, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - Somer Villa: Waller Smith, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Sunbright: Potomac Joint Stock Land Bank, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Allport, Pearl: 50 acres, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Donohue, Mr.: 226 acres, 1930's (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Mahoney, Margaret: 608 acres, 1936-1938 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Miller, Haywood H.: 494 acres, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Nelson, Lewis P.: 1000 acres, 1940-1941 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Summerville, Martha: 549 acres, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1934-1939, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Cumberland County (Box 23-24)
      - Ashton: John R. Blanton, 1936-1939 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Clifton: Wistar Anderson, 1935-1936 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Clifton: Robert Toomay, Jr., 1969 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Glintwar: Halle Sutton, 1935-1936 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - High Bridge Farm: Mr. Dixon, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Locust Level: Luther B. Franck, 1944-1949 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Mount Elba: Mrs. Terrill, 1939-1941 (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - Mount View: W.B. Clark (realtor), 1970 (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - Muddy Creek Mills: M.E. Blanton, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - Newstead Farm: B.B. Ford, 1934 (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - Northfield: John Springer Gray, 1940-1941 (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - Northfield: Mr. Midgette, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Oakland: H.H. Hudgins, 1934 (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - Resthaven: William M. Flippin, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - Snead Dairy Farm: Nash P. Snead, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - Trice Lake: A.B. Hardee, 1935, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - Gilkerson, Taylor: 8 acres, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Goodman, Herbert: 386 acres, 1937 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Patrick, N.R.: 307 acres, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Talley, Joe: 186 acres, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1934-1940 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Dinwiddie County (Box 24, Folder 7-16)
      - Georgian Motel: M.D. Goodrich, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Greenfields: R.B. Walton, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Laurel Brook: S.G. Morton, 1941-1942 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Mansfield: Central Hanover Bank and Trust Company, 1936 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Mansfield: M.D. Goodrich, 1938-1955 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Whippernock: M.D. Goodrich, 1952-1954 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Whippernock: E.H. Titmus, Jr., 1972 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Woodstock Hall: A.L. Seay, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1938-1939 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Elizabeth City County (Box 25, Folder 1-4)
      - Buckroe Beach: 1932-1937 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Grand View: L.R. Carson, 1934-1936 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Rishel, O.T.: 9 1/2 acres, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1933-1954 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Essex County (Box 25-27)
      - Bathurst Farm: George B. Krieter, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Baylors Mill: H.L. Baylor, 1936-1939 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Cloverdale Farm: 220 acres, 1933-1934 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Cloverfield Farm: Fritz Keck, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Creek Side: H.L. Lorraine, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Greenfield Farm or Kinloch Farm: Robert W. Baylor, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Greenfield: J.C. Phillips, 1948-1951 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Holly Spring: 13 3/4 acres, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Hollywood: William H. Jeffries, 1941-1945 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Kill Kare: Catesby Ware, 1925-1943 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Kill Kare: Anderson Flemming, 1925, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Kinloch: L.M. Williams, 1936 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Lindon: David J. Friedman, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Meadow: A.D. Latane, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Moore Wright House: 1941 (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Mount Clement: Clagett H. Pattie, 1940-1948 (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - Mount Landing Farm: Mrs. Meister, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - Mount Prospect: Stella P. Pond, 1939-1941 (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - Payne Island: F.L.W. Green, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Phillips' Dairy: Mr. Phillips, 1930's (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Rackeys: Maurice Weinstein, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Shelby: W.H. Smith, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Small Hall: Henri Claiborne, 1963-1968 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - South Hill: n.d. (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Sunnyside: Susie W. Maddox, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Anderton: 1941-1943 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Baughan, J.A.: 237 acres, 1942 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Breeden, Cecil J.: 65 acres, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Coleman: 3 acres, 1942 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Courtney, William R., Jr.: 68 acres, 1962-1963 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Dickenson, Forest: church, 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Dryden, W.A.: 1954-1957 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Harper, Jean: n.d. (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Heindle, W.S. (realtor): 130 acres, 1951-1952 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Howell, B.N.: 1967 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Latane, A.D.: 1944 (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Latane, A.D.: 165 acres, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 19)
      - Latane, A.D.: 1941-1956 (Box 26, Folder 20)
      - Maddox, Mrs.: 1941 (Box 26, Folder 21)
      - Mitchell, B.G.: 172 acres, 1964-1965 (Box 26, Folder 22)
      - Mitchell, Mrs.: 66 acres, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 23)
      - Parker: 1942-1952 (Box 26, Folder 24)
      - Parker: 172 1/2 acres, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 25)
      - Parkinson, W.W.: 1957 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Silver, Carl: 1948 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Spindle, Emily: 1948-1956 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Waring, Dabney T.: 32 acres, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Wright, Captain Ed: 1949 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1931-1942, 1967, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Unidentified residence: photographs, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Unidentified residence: photographs, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Fairfax County (Box 27, Folder 10-20)
      - Bannockburn Farm: Harry Blake, 1935-1936 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Buell Dairy Farm and Bready Farm: Arthur A. Buell and George A. Bready, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Hollin Hall: H.P. Wilson, 1936-1938 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Ridgelawn: Percy L. Crosby, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Spring Bank: E.S. Sweebey, 1934 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Woodlawn: Mrs. Oscar W. Underwood, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Smith, Rita: 10 acres and 20 acres, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Turner, Scott: 243 acres, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 17)
      - Walton: 140 acres, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1931-1941 (Box 27, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Fauquier County (Box 27-28)
      - Alwington: Walter A. Hitchcock, 1937-1940 (Box 27, Folder 21)
      - Barrymore: Bedford F. Fishback, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 22)
      - Belle Meade: Dr. S.B. Elliott, 1935-1938 (Box 27, Folder 23)
      - Bellevue: Mrs. Baldwin, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 24)
      - Bollingbrook: T.B. Glascock, 1945-1948 (Box 27, Folder 25)
      - Belvoir: Fairfax Harrison, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 26)
      - Carter Hall: C.A. Heineken, 1935 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Covert of Crest Hill Farm: F.W. Sharpe & Son, 1942 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Delaplane: C.L. Delaplane, 1936-1939 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Fairfield: E. Marshall Newton, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Hawthorne Farm: Ian S. Montgomery & Company (realtor), 1956 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Leeds Manor: Fred Sharp, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - North Rock: W. Purdue Owens, 1956-1959 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Scott's Mill Property: n.d. (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - View Tree Farm: Crosby Miller, 1948-1949 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Vint Hill Farm: Fidelity-Philadelphia Trust Company, 1938-1939 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - Jenkins, Edward E.: 65 acres, 1930's (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Keidal, L.A.: 3670 acres, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - Palmer, Howard: 500 acres, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Thompson, G.R.: 1534 acres, 1937 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1933-1970 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Floyd County (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - Floyd Dairy Farm: Homer Wilson, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Fluvanna County (Box 28-30)
      - Carysbrook: Henry Jones, 1940-1941 (Box 28, Folder 18)
      - Carysbrook: J.W. Holland, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Chatham: Martha Maynard, 1941-1945 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Chatham: Henry B. Caldwell, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Glen Arvon Farm: Potomac Joint Stock Land Bank, 1932-1936 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Glen Burnie: Horatio Bigelow, 1948-1960 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Hill Grove Farm: National Bank & Trust Company, 1962-1963 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Hunter's Lodge: Vida K. Long, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Lower Bremo: Cary H. Cocke, 1944-1963 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Melrose: Mrs. John Griffin, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Mount Airy: Daisy A. Seay, 1946-1952 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - Oakland: J. Perry Longworth, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - Pleasant Grove: S.O. Van Arsdale, 1943-1948 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Point of Fork: J. Alston Cabell, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Roadview: Roy E. Perkins, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - Solitude: W.H. Hannah, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 15)
      - Wilmington: Floyd H. Fry, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - Cox, J.H.: 130 acres, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Haden: 1956 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Harvey, D.F.: 56 acres, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Johnson: 12 acres, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Mays, J.F.: 392 acres, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Roberts, G.W.: 525 acres, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Sykes, W.A.: 190 acres, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Tucker, R.B.: 13 acres, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Webb, Frank E.: 210 acres, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1932-1939 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Franklin County (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings: 1940, 1953, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Frederick County (Box 30, Folder 13-15)
      - Waverly: J.W. Robinson, 1937 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Offen, Henry: 1954 (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Fredericksburg (Box 30, Folder 16-18)
      - Betty Washington Inn: 1960 (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - Sneed, N.K., III: 1966 (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1936, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Giles County (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - Virginia Historic Buildings Survey real estate listings (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Gloucester County (Box 31-42)
      - Abingdon Glebe: George Lamberth, 1942 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Airville: Mrs. Stanley, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Bay Top or Capahosic Hall: William V. West, 1934-1944 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Bell Lodge Farm: J.B. Taylor, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Belleterre: H.E. Thomas, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 5)